Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5
- Salinas Citizens Committee in Defense of Farm Workers, 1973; Publication (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Farmworkers Build Their Union: Si Se Puede!, Publication (Box 35, Folder 14)
    By Salinas Citizens Committee in Defense of Farmworkers. Newsletter. Item is in English;Spanish.
- San Francisco State (College) Strike Support Committee On Strike, 1969; Publication (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: On Strike Shut It Down, Publication (Box 35, Folder 15)
    By SF State Strike Committee. Newsletter. Item is in SF.
- Self Defense Committee of the 17 Smith Act Victims, 1952; Publication (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Pettis perry: The Story of a Working Class Leader, Publication (Box 35, Folder 16)
    By Richard O. Boyer. Item is in English.
- Socialist Labor Party. American Section. Labor and Capitol, 1892; Publication (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Labor and Capital and The Object of Labor Movement, Publication (Box 35, Folder 17)
    By G.A. Hoehn. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Socialist Labor Party. National Executive Comm, Publication (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Craft Unionism versus industrial Unionism, Publication (Box 35, Folder 18)
    By Socialist Labor Party. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Socialist Labor Party. National Executive Committee. International May Day, 1910; Publication (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: International May Day and American Labor Day, Publication (Box 35, Folder 19)
- The Socialist Party (U.S.) Address to labor 191u, Publication (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: An Address to Labor, Publication (Box 35, Folder 20)
    By The Socialist Party. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- Socialist Workers Party. America's Permanent Depression, 1938; Publication (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: America's Permanent Depression: The Truth About Employment, Publication (Box 35, Folder 21)
    By Art Preis. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Socialist Workers Party. Build a labor party, 1946; Publication (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Build a labor Party Now, Publication (Box 35, Folder 22)
    By George Clarke. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Socialist Workers Party. Socialis Workers Part proposes, 1976; Publication (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: A Bill of Rights for working people for protection from soaring prices, layoffs, wars, racial oppression, and sexism, Publication (Box 35, Folder 23)
    By Socialist Workers Party. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Socialist Workers Party. Stalinists on the waterfront / by Art Preis, 1947; Publication (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Stalinists on The Waterfront, Publication (Box 35, Folder 24)
- Socialist Workers Party. Wall Street's war, not ours! / by Joe Hansen, 1940; Publication (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: wall Street's War: Not Ours!, Publication (Box 35, Folder 25)
    By Joe Hansen. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Society for Personnel Administration. Union are here to stay, 1962; Publication (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Unions Are Here To Stay: A Guide for Employee-Management Relations in the Federal Service, Publication (Box 35, Folder 26)
    By Ann Holland. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Southern School for Workers, Inc. Southern workers speak, 1942; Publication (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Southern Workers Speak, Publication (Box 35, Folder 27)
    By Southern School for Workers Inc. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Southern Workers Defense Committee. To live and die in Dixie / by Robert Wood, 1935; Publication (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: To Live and Die in Dixie, Publication (Box 35, Folder 28)
    By Robert Wood. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Standard Oil Company. Three men in a boat, 1962; Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Three Men in a Boat, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
    By M.J. Rathbone. Address. Item is in English.
- Students for a Democratic Society. SDS work-in 1968: toward a worker-student alliance, Publication (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: SDS Work0In 1968: Towards a Worker-Student Alliance, Publication (Box 35, Folder 30)
    By Students for a Democratic Society. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Tanners' Council of America. Real threat of communism, 1950; Publication (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: The Real Threat of Communism to American Labor Relations, Publication (Box 35, Folder 31)
    By Tanners' Council of America. Item is in English.
- The Thermos Co. - Hourly employee handbook and safety rules, Publication (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Hourly Employee Handbook and Safety Ruls, Publication (Box 35, Folder 32)
    By The Thermos Co. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Timken Service Bureau. Industrial Department. Compromise methods, 1926; Publication (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: For Workers and Their Employers, Publication (Box 35, Folder 33)
    By Timken Service Bureau. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Trade Union Education League - Struggle of the Trade, Publication (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Struggle of the Trade Unions Against Facism, Publication (Box 35, Folder 34)
    By Trade Union Educational League. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Union of Democratic Filipinos. Memorial for Silme Domingo, 1982; Publication (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: A Memorial for Silme Domingo and Gene Viernes, Publication (Box 35, Folder 35)
    By Union of Democratic Filipinos. Flyer. Item is in English.
- United Labor Party. Will Walter Reuther start a labor party?, 1949; Publication (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Will Walter Reuther Start a Labor Party?, Publication (Box 35, Folder 36)
    By Steve Martin. Booklet. Item is in English.
- United States. Steel Corporation. Industrial Relations for the future / by R. Heath Larry, 1960; Publication (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: An Appraisal of Collective bargaining in a Free Society, Publication (Box 35, Folder 37)
    By R. Conrad Cooper. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- United States Steel Corporation. Public Relations Dept. Appraisal of collective bargaining, 1967; Publication (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Technical Paper, Publication (Box 35, Folder 38)
    By R. Heath Larry. Booklet. Item is in English.
- United States. Anthracite Coal Strike Commission. Anthracite Board of Coalition. Award of the Anthracite Coal Strike, 1916; Publication (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Award of the Anthracite Coal Strike Commission, Publication (Box 35, Folder 39)
    By United States Anthracite Coal Strike Commission. Item is in English.
- United States. Bureau of Education. - Industrial Education, Publication (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Industrial Education in The South, Publication (Box 35, Folder 40)
    By Rev.A.D. Mayo. Booklet. Item is in English.
- United States. Civil Service Commission. Bureau of Intergovernmental Personnel Programs. Job Analysis, 1973; Publication (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Job Analysis: Key to Better Management, Publication (Box 35, Folder 41)
    By United States Civil Service Commission. Booklet. Item is in English.
- United States. Department of the Interior. Fish and Wildlife Service. Bureau of Commercial Fisheries. Economic, 1966; Publication (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: An Economic Study of the Boston Large-Trawler Labor Force, Publication (Box 35, Folder 42)
    By United States Department of the Interior: Fish and Wildlife Service. Booklet. Item is in English.
- United States. Committee on Economic Security. Security / [by] Franklin D. Roosevelt, Frances Perkins, Harry L. Hopkins, 1934; Publication (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Security, Publication (Box 35, Folder 43)
    By Franklin D. Roosevelt, Frances Perkins, Harry L. Hopkins, Dr. Frank P. Graham, Daniel C. Roper and Harold B. Butler. Item is in English.
- United States. Department of Labor. Library Recent literature on unemployment, 1921; Publication (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Recent Literature on Unemployment with Particular Reference to Causes and Remediies, Publication (Box 35, Folder 44)
    By United States Department of Labor Library. Item is in English.
- United States. Department of Labor. Wage and Hour Division. Ceiling for hours, a floor for wages., 1938; Publication (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: A Ceiling for Hours a Floor for Wages and a Break for Children, Publication (Box 35, Folder 45)
    By Frances Perkins. Booklet. Item is in English.
- United States. Dept. of Labor. Women's Bureau. British Policies and Methods, Publication (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: British Policies and Methods in Employing Women in Wartime, Publication (Box 35, Folder 46)
    By Janet M. Hooks. Item is in English.
- United States. Department of Labor. Working Conditions Service. How to give illustrated, Publication (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: How to Give illustrated Lectures on Accident Prevention to Workmen, Publication (Box 35, Folder 47)
    By United States Department of Labor. Item is in English.
- United States. Federal Emergency Management Agency, Publication (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Your Family Disaster Plan, Publication (Box 35, Folder 48)
    By United States Federal Emergency Management Agency. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- United States. National Labor Relations Board. Information to voters in elections conducted, 1962; Publication (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Information to Voters in Elections Counducted by the National Labor Relations Board, Publication (Box 35, Folder 49)
    By United States National Labor Relations Board. Item is in English.
- United States. National Labor Relations Board. Jurisdictional guide / National Labor Relations Board, 1960; Publication (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Jurisdictional Guide, Publication (Box 35, Folder 50)
    By United States National Labor Relations Board. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- United States. National Labor Relations Board. Layman's Guide to basic law under the National Labor Relations Act, 1964; Publication (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: A layman's guide to basic law under the National Labor Relations Act, Publication (Box 35, Folder 51)
    By United States National Labor Relations Board. Booklet. Item is in English.
- United States. National Labor Relations Board. What you should know about the regional offices, 1962; Publication (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: What you should know about the Regional Offices of the National Labor Relations Board, Publication (Box 35, Folder 52)
- United States. President's Committee on Government Contracts. Sixth report to President Eisenhower from the Committee on Government Contracts, 1959; Publication (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Sixth Report, Publication (Box 35, Folder 53)
    By United States President's Committee on Government Contracts. Booklet. Item is in English.
- United States. President's Committee on Youth Employment. Challenge of jobless youth, 1963; Publication (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: The Challenge of Jobless Youth, Publication (Box 35, Folder 54)
    By United States President's Committee on Youth Employment. Booklet. Item is in English.
- United States. President's Mediation Commission. Report of President's Mediation Commission to the President of the United States., 1918; Publication (Box 35, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: U.S. President's mediation commission, Publication (Box 35, Folder 55)
    By United States President's Mediation Commission. Booklet. Item is in English.
- United States. Social Security Board. Federal Security Agency. Labor Information, 1944; Publication (Box 35, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: The Units of Organized Labor and How They Are Related, Publication (Box 35, Folder 56)
    By Federal Security Agency - Social Security Board. Item is in English.
- United States. War manpower Commission. Bureau of Manpower Utilization. Division of Occupational Analysis. Occupational analysis publications July 1945, Publication (Box 35, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Occupational Analysis Publications, Publication (Box 35, Folder 57)
    By War Manpower Commission: Bureau of Manpower Utilization Division of Occupational Analysis. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- United States. War Manpower Commission. Bureau of Training. Training woman power, 1943; Publication (Box 35, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Training Womanpower, Publication (Box 35, Folder 58)
    By War Manpower Commission. Booklet. Item is in English.
- United Workers Party of America. What next for the American Workers, 1934; Publication (Box 35, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: What Next for the American Workers?, Publication (Box 35, Folder 59)
    By United Workers' Party of America. Item is in English.
- United Workers of America. World-wide fascism or world revolution?, 1934; Publication (Box 35, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: World-Wide Fascism or World Revolution?, Publication (Box 35, Folder 60)
- University of Iowa. College of Business Administration. Bureau of Labor and Management. Guidelines for employee training, 1963; Publication (Box 35, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Guidelines for Employee Training, Publication (Box 35, Folder 61)
    By Don R. Sheriff. Item is in English.
- University of Iowa. College of Business Administration. Bureau of Labor and Management. Job enlargement, 1963; Publication (Box 35, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Job Enlargement: A Case Study, Publication (Box 35, Folder 62)
    By J.F. Biggane and Paul A. Stewart. Item is in English.
- University of Iowa. College of Business Administration. Bureau of Labor and Management. Social and Technological Revolution of the Sixties, 1965; Publication (Box 35, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: The Social and Technological Revolution of the Sixties, Publication (Box 35, Folder 63)
    By University of Iowa - College of Business Administration - Bureau of Labor and Management. Booklet. Item is in English.
- University of Nevada. Dept. of Mechanical and Electrical Engineering. Proceedings of the first annual industrial safety conference, 1914; Publication (Box 35, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: The Proceeding of the First Annual Industrial Safety Conference, Publication (Box 35, Folder 64)
    By University of Nevada - Dept. Of Mechanical and Electrical Engineering. Book. Item is in English.
- University of Pittsburgh. Graduate School of Public and International Affairs. Labor policies and the development of international trade, 1966; Publication (Box 35, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Labor Policies and the Development of International Trade, Publication (Box 35, Folder 65)
    By David A. Morse. Item is in English.
- University of Wisconsin. University Extension Division. School for Workers, 1959; Publication (Box 35, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: The School for Workers, Publication (Box 35, Folder 66)
    By University of Wisconsin - University Extension Division. Item is in English.
- W.E. Upjohn Institute for Community Research. Guaranteed annual wage and business stabilization, 1955; Publication (Box 35, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: The Guaranteed Annual Wage and Business Stabilization, Publication (Box 35, Folder 67)
    By W.E. Upjohn Institute for Community Research. Item is in English.
- W.E. Upjohn Institute for Community Research Position paper of the paper industry in the economy of Kalamazoo County, Michigan, 1954; Publication (Box 35, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: The Position of the Paper Industry in the Economy of Kalamazoo County Michigan in 1954, Publication (Box 35, Folder 68)
- W.E. Upjohn Institute for Community Research. Pre-requisites for a guaranteed annual wage, 1956; Publication (Box 35, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Prerequisites for a Guaranteed Annual Wage, Publication (Box 35, Folder 69)
- W.E. Upjohn Institute for Employment Research. Management in the scientific age, 1958; Publication (Box 35, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Management in the Scientific Age: A Conference of the Washington Chapter Society for Advancement of Management, Publication (Box 35, Folder 70)
- Waterfront Employers Union of San Francisco. Pacific Coast Longshoremen's Strike of 1934, Publication (Box 35, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: The pacific Coast Longshormen;s Strike of 1934, Publication (Box 35, Folder 71)
    By Thomas G. Plant. Item is in English.
- William Roy Smith Memorial Fund. How can a union build its program?, 1940; Publication (Box 35, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: How Can A Union Build It's Program?, Publication (Box 35, Folder 72)
    By William Roy Smith Memorial Fund. Item is in English.
- Workers Alliance of California. Factual statement of Workers Alliance of California, 1939; Publication (Box 35, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: We Were Investigated, Publication (Box 35, Folder 73)
    By Workers Alliance of California. Item is in English.
- Workers Library Publishers. Why every miner should be a Communist / by John Pepper, 1928; Publication (Box 35, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Why evert Miner should be a Communist, Publication (Box 35, Folder 74)
    By John Pepper. Item is in English.
- Workers Party. Incentive pay: the speed-up new style / by Albert Gates, 1941; Publication (Box 35, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Incentive Pay, Publication (Box 35, Folder 75)
    By Albert Gates. Item is in English.
- Workers Party - Question of unity: between the Workers Party and the Socialist Workers Party / by Albert Goldman, 1947; Publication (Box 35, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: The Question of Unity, Publication (Box 35, Folder 76)
    By Albert Goldman. Item is in English.
- Workers Party. Election Campaign Committee. How to get jobs for all, 1940; Publication (Box 35, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: How to Get Jobs for All, Publication (Box 35, Folder 77)
    By Workers Party. Item is in English.
- Workers Party of America. Blood and Steel: an exposure of the 12-hour day in the steel industry / by Jay Lovestone, 1920; Publication (Box 35, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Blood and Steel: An Exposure of the 12-Hour Day in the steel industry, Publication (Box 35, Folder 78)
    By Jay Lovestone. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Workers Party of America. Program and constitution, Workers party of America, 1921; Publication (Box 35, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Program and Constitution: Workers Party of America, Publication (Box 35, Folder 79)
    By Workers' Party of America. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Working Party of America. Underground radicalism: an open letter to Eugene V. Debs, 1923; Publication (Box 35, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Underground Racialism, Publication (Box 35, Folder 80)
- Workers Party of America. Unemployment: why it occurs and how to fight it, 1924; Publication (Box 35, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: Unemployment: Why it occurs and How to Fight It, Publication (Box 35, Folder 81)
    By Earl R. Browder. Item is in English.
- Workers Party of U.S. War and the workers / by John West, 1935; Publication (Box 35, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: War and the Workers, Publication (Box 35, Folder 82)
    By John West. Item is in English.
- Workers Party of U.S.A. Role of the trade unions: the economic, 1945; Publication (Box 35, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: The Role of the Trade Unions: Their Economic Role Under Capitalism, Publication (Box 35, Folder 83)
    By Workers' Party of America. Item is in English.
- Workers Party of U.S.A. National Education Dept. Problems of party education, 1946; Publication (Box 35, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Problems of Party Education: A Guide to Educational Work, Publication (Box 35, Folder 84)
    By Workers' Party of the U.S.A. Item is in English.
- Workers Party of U.S.A. National Education Dept. Workers Party and the transitional program / by Ernest Erber, 1946; Publication (Box 35, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: The Workers Party and the Transitional Program, Publication (Box 35, Folder 85)
    By Ernest Erber. Item is in English.
- Young Workers Communist League. Challenge of youth, 1926; Publication (Box 35, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: The Challenge of Youth, Publication (Box 35, Folder 86)
    By Sam Darcy. Item is in English.
- Allegheny Airline, Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 18th Annual Report 1955, Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
    By Allegheny Airline. Item is in English.
- American Airlines - Annuals reports, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Annual Report: Year ended December 31, 1949, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
    By American Airlines. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Annual Report: Year Ended December 31, 1950, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Annual Report 1951, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Annual Report 1952, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Annual Report 1953, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Annual Report 1956, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Annual Report 1955, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Annual Report 1957, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Annual Report 1954, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
- American Airlines - Customer Service Dept., Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Airlines Ticketing System - Questions and Answers, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By American Airlines - Customer Service Dept. Letter. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Procedural Revisions, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Highlights, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By American Airlines - Customer Service Dept. August 17, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Time Limits, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By American Airlines - Customer Service Dept. Sep 16/56. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: American Airlines Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By American Airlines - Customer Service Dept. August 6, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Highlights, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Highlights, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By American Airlines - Customer Service Dept. August 17, 1956 Revision No. 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: American Airlines Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By American Airlines - Customer Service Dept. August 30, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Highlights, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By American Airlines - Customer Service Dept. Rvision No. 3, September 16, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Highlights, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By American Airlines - Customer Service Dept. Rev. No. 21, August 17, 1956. Item is in English.
- American Airlines - Employee Information, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Inventroy Questionaire, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By American Airlines - Employee Information. Form. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Management Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By American Airlines - Employee Information. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Summary of Appraisal Interview, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Quarterly Enter-On and Removal Report, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Welcome to American, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By American Airlines - Employee Information. Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
- American Airlines - Management Devel. Dept., Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Management Candidate, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By American Airlines - Management Level Department. Booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Management Candidate Guide, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By American Airlines - Management Level Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Management Candidate Staff Orientation, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By American Airlines - Management Level Department. June 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Guide to the Appraisal Process, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Guide to the Appraisal Process, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By American Airlines - Management Level Department. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: American Airlines management Development Program - Introduction, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Phase 11: Group Appraisal, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Proposals for American Airlines Management Training, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
- American Airlines - Organization Charts, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)